bookvip.com 2017-06-06

# BookVIP.com - Cheapest Vacation Packages To The Most Popular Destinations

Toll Free  
**1-(888)-849-8450  
1-(407)-964-3007 **

Over 3.5 Million Likes 

3,595,024 Facebook Likes and counting.  
People love our offers, you will too!

×

Request a free call back

To talk with us, please enter your phone number.

(You'll will need an open phone line to receive this call)

Country:

Your Number:

( ) \- 

**BookVIP.com Privacy Policy and Terms of USE**

By using or calling this web site, I expressly consent and request that BookVIP.com, contact me via telephone at the number(s) I call from or contact information I provide using sms text message or automated telephone dialing system, prerecorded message, electronic mail. Concerning my travel interests. 

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for BookVIP.com. 

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

1.

What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

2.

What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

3.

The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

4.

How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

•

See what data we have about you, if any.

•

Change/correct any data we have about you.

•

Have us delete any data we have about you.

•

Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Taxes & Fees**

The taxes are tax recovery charges BookVIP.com pays to its vendors (e.g. hotels); We retain our service fees as compensation in servicing your travel reservation.

**PREPAID HOTEL RESERVATIONS**

You acknowledge that BookVIP.com pre-negotiate certain room rates with hotel suppliers to facilitate the booking of reservations. You also acknowledge that BookVIP.com provide you services to facilitate such booking of reservations for a consideration (the "facilitation fee"). The room rate displayed on the Website is a combination of the pre-negotiated room rate for rooms reserved on your behalf by BookVIP.com and the facilitation fee retained by BookVIP.com for their services. You authorize BookVIP.com to book reservations for the total reservation price, which includes the room rate displayed on the Website, plus tax recovery charges, service fees, and where applicable, taxes on BookVIP.com services. You acknowledge that except as provided below with respect to tax obligations on the amounts we retain for our services, BookVIP.com do not collect taxes for remittance to applicable taxing authorities. The tax recovery charges on prepaid hotel transactions are a recovery of the estimated taxes (e.g. sales and use, occupancy, room tax, excise tax, value added tax, etc.) that BookVIP.com pay to the hotel supplier for taxes due on the hotel's rental rate for the room. The hotel suppliers invoice BookVIP.com for certain charges, including tax amounts. The hotel suppliers are responsible for remitting applicable taxes to the applicable taxing jurisdictions. BookVIP.com does not act as co-vendors with the supplier with whom we book or reserve our customer's travel reservations.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**Company Address**

975 North Miami Beach Blvd,  
North Miami, FL 33162
